ARINZE PETER CHINEDU

PYTHON DEVELOPER

I am an adaptable professional developer with 4+ years of experience and a proven knowledge in blending the art of design with the skill of programming, real time data, data security and responsive web design, to deliver engaging user experience through efficient website development, proactive feature optimization, and relentless debugging. Aiming to leverage my skills to successfully fill the software development role in your company.

EDUCATION

January 2015 - September 2019. Nnamdi Azikiwe University. Awka, Nigeria.

Bachelor of Science, computer Science. Honors: cum laude (GPA: 4.1/5.0).

RELEVANT SKILLS

- ❖ PYTHON
- DJANGO
- ❖ REST API
 - ❖ NUMPY
 - ❖ MYSQL
- ❖ POSTGRES
 - GIT
 - ❖ GITHUB
 - DOCKER
 - HEROKU
 - AWS
- DIGITAL OCEAN
 - HTML
 - CSS
 - ❖ BOOTSTRAP
 - JAVASCRIPT
 - REACT
 - UI/UX
 - > PHOTOSHOP
 - FIGMA

CONTACT

Phone: (+234) 903-280-6278 Whatsapp: (+234) 812-718-5011

Skype: https://join.skype.com/invite/HfuVGUMZNaQm

Email: <u>breezeconcept3@gmail.com</u> **Github:** https://github.com/Mr-IRobot/

My Website: https://breeze-portfolio.netlify.app/

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/breeze-s-concept-578a6b1b5

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:

SEP 2019 - Present

CEO

BREEZE CONCEPT, AWKA, NIGERIA.

- Managed a small scale firm that offers services to businesses and individuals
- We help these businesses to scale up by providing an online presence for their products and services.

SEP 2019 - Present

Frontend web developer

Breeze concept, Awka, Nigeria.

- Developed landing pages, dashboards and online applications using HTML/CSS, Bootstrap and Javascript.
- Developed designs to meet specific requirements such as quickloading sites with particular.

September 2021 - January 2022 Backend web developer

KLIQ, Lagos, Nigeria.

 Developed an e-commerce website that uses data analytics to visualize the data on products available and showcases a statistical report on the data.

SOME WORK REFERENCE:

Business website: https://niffas-beauty-hub.netlify.app/
Affiliate marketing website: www.kliqaffiliate.com
To see more of my works - Visit: https://breeze-hub.netlify.app/

portfolio.netlify.app/

CERTIFICATION

September 2019
BSc in Computer science and programming
Nnamdi Azikiwe University